Liang Zhiqiang!
Why are you still looking for my son?
Say something!
A Qiang, stay back!
You know what I want.
Mong Kok Tenth Street.
I'll be waiting for you.
A Qiang.
I trust you.
But remember this.
If you break the law,
I'll be the first to arrest you.
Let me go!
A Qiang!
You wanna die?!
Brother Qiang, look here!
Hit him!
Top Enforcer!
Come on!
Xie Guanhong!
Come at me if you have a problem!
She has nothing to do with this!
Leave the family out of it.
That line is so cliché.
I like it.
I could let her go.
But I don't know if the boys will agree.
No way!
Brother Qiang, your chick is so hot.
Be generous.
Stay here tonight and keep me company.
Have a little chat.
I'm so lonely.
You're crazy.
I advise you not to do anything rash.
I'm begging you.
We've been brothers our whole lives.
I've never heard you beg anyone before.
Top Enforcer.
A Qiang.
Don't hit him!
I'm begging you, stop hitting him.
Stop hitting him!
I'm begging you!
A Qiang!
Don't hit him!
Thrilling, isn't it?
Let her go.
Take my life instead.
Chen Haonan.
Little Stutterer.
Then I'm Crow.
No.
Liang Zhiqiang, why would I want your life?
I just want what's mine.
No!
You can't give it to him.
Don't give it to him.
We need the USB drive to convict him.
Liang Zhiqiang, don't give it to him.
Shut up!
Stop hitting her!
Stop it!
It's okay.
A Qiang.
Stay alive.
Damn it!
Brother Qiang, run!
To be honest, I was scared at first.
I was afraid you were in a triad.
Brother Qiang is in the game.
I hate triads.
I didn't want anything to do with them.
But...
When I saw you always alone,
always staying silent,
always keeping your head down,
looking so pitiful in the corner...
That's when I knew
you were different from them.
I'm sorry.
I promise you I'll live a good life.
You won't return to the old path.
Now you have me.
And the flower shop.
The flower shop is your home.
We are your home.
Let's go back to the flower shop, okay?
Back to the flower shop, okay?
Brother Qiang, hurry!
The police are already here!
If we don't leave now, it's too late!
Brother Qiang!
Brother Qiang, let's go!
Let's go!
Let's go, Brother Qiang!
Go!
The deceased's name is Wang Danni.
She was a teacher at Lishan Welfare Academy.
The preliminary cause of death is a fall.
We suspect she was involved in a gang conflict.
Nearby residents witnessed
an armed brawl on the rooftop.
Based on the testimony,
the confirmed participants
are mostly Heyisheng members.
A witness stated
that a core member of Heyisheng,
Liang Zhiqiang,
after the body fell,
made direct contact with the body.
He is now listed as the prime suspect.
Alright.
Seal off the scene immediately.
There has been a recent surge in violent crimes,
severely impacting the public's quality of life.
Our Harbor City West Kowloon Major Crimes Unit
and the Anti-Triad Unit
will join forces with the mainland police
to form a special task force.
On behalf of the West Kowloon Police Station, I promise
that we will solve this case as soon as possible
and give the public an answer.
I hereby announce
the official launch of the Second Portland Street Operation.
Where is Xie Guanhong?
I'm a man of loyalty.
I'm just a...
I'm just a lookout.
No, Brother Qiang.
I'm just a receptionist.
I don't know anything.
Brother Qiang.
I...
I'm just a nobody, Brother Qiang!
Please don't, Brother Qiang!